Finding Aid for the Bob Brown Papers LSC.0723
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Notes--short piece on Blast and little magazines. (Box 102)
- Pamphlet--Writers Take Sides: Are You For or Against Franco and Fascism?. (Box 102)
- Personal Library--Ten O'Clock, by J.A.M. Whistler. (Box 102)
- Bibliography--Books by Bob Brown. (Box 103)
- Clippings. (Box 103)
- Correspondence. (Box 103)
- Correspondence--Letter from J. Jones (18 pp.). (Box 103)
- Correspondence--Letter from Paul Bowles. (Box 103)
- Correspondence--Note from W.H Auden. (Box 103)
- Ephemera. (Box 103)
- Notebooks. (Box 103)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 103)
- Notes--Books and I Are Bound. (Box 103)
- Notes--on symptoms of an undiagnosed condition. (Box 103)
- Poetry--"Beautiful Star". (Box 103)
- Poetry--"I have peed in a pail". (Box 103)
- Poetry--Drafts. (Box 103)
- Poetry--Exceedingly Shy. (Box 103)
- Poetry--The English Lesson. (Box 103)
- Poetry--The Poor Working Girl. (Box 103)
- Proposal for a book of literary portraits. (Box 103)
- Publication--CONTEMPO: A Bob Brown Issue. (Box 103)
- Ephemera--travel timetables. (Box 104)
- Leather Book Cover. (Box 104)
- Manuscript--Congress Signs Off For the Summer. (Box 104)
- Manuscript--Doggie Can You Spare a Bone, by Bob Brown. (Box 104)
- Manuscript--Girls Go Modern in Brazil, by Rose Brown. (Box 104)
- Manuscript--Going Native Right at Home, by Bob Brown. (Box 104)
- Manuscript--I Win Your Story Prize, by Bob Brown. (Box 104)
- Manuscript--Marriages Are Made in Heaven. (Box 104)
- Manuscript--Reading Kay Boyle. (Box 104)
- Manuscripts (incomplete). (Box 104)
- Manuscript--Taming the Tiger, by Rose Brown. (Box 104)
- Manuscript--The Vehling Collection of Books and Documents on Food and Feeding and Hotel Keeping. (Box 104)
- Manuscript--Viva A Villa Barcellos. (Box 104)
- Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 104)
- Notes--blurbs for "Let There Be Beer!". (Box 104)
- Notes--on Ezra Pound. (Box 104)
- Poetry--Drafts. (Box 104)
- Poetry--Nature Poem by a Native of Nice. (Box 104)
- Poetry--On With the Walkathon. (Box 104)
- Poetry--Owed to Our Independence. (Box 104)
- Proposal--A Popular Project for Santarem's SESP Hospital. (Box 104)
- Bibliographic information and correspondence. (Box 105)
- Correspondence and clippings. (Box 105)
- Correspondence, notes, and clippings. (Box 105)
- Correspondence, notes, and manuscripts. (Box 105)
- Manuscript--Bringing up Chico by Rose Brown. (Box 105)
- Manuscript--Jews on the Run. (Box 105)
- Manuscript--Professional Americans by Bob Brown. (Box 105)
- Manuscripts, clippings, and notes. (Box 105)
- Manuscripts, clippings, and notes. (Box 105)
- Manuscripts, clippings, and notes. (Box 105)
- Manuscripts, clippings, and notes. (Box 105)
- Manuscript--The Dinosaur's Egg by Bob Brown. (Box 105)
- Manuscript--The Great Tichborne Romance by Bob Brown. (Box 105)
- Manuscript--Wall Street or Bust. (Box 105)
- Notes/Scrap paper. (Box 105)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Apollinaire in the Hair"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Autos Roll Around"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Both Your Arms and Both Your Legs"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Bullet, Bell, Head"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Cheap Ambitions will be God"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Come Seven!"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Cupids Have Made Public"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Decoration"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Diminuette"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Drawing"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Eyes on the Half-Shell"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("God Bless You For Your Spirals"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Grapes and Beards"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Great Gobs of Subtlety"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Here They Come, The Bipeds"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Hirsute"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("His Muddy Shoes"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("I Am the Little Wooden-Faced Puppet"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("I Hate Prize Fights"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("I have written out of my heart"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("I Must Tell You Dear"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("I Preen My Quills"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("I Stroke the Paper With My Pen"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("I Want! I Want!"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Iron Moulds for Men"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Is It a Cardinal Sin"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Lady Fingers"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Life Professor Comedy"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Lips Carmine"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Making Honey"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Man Moulded of Common Clay"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Mice Tracks"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Missionaries"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("My Fly Speck"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("My Mosque"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("My Mouth Full of Kisses"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("My Skeleton"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Orchids"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Pagliacci"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Paris and the Golden Apple"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Paris in Pairs"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Paris Vocal, 1929"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Pousse-Café"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Prohibition"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Salon 1929"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Spawn"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Taking Art"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("The Peasant Poet's Earnest Prayer to God"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("The Staff of Life"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("The World is My Oyster"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("There is Still Life"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("To My Son"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Tongues of Flame"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("TV Poet-Tree"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Venus + Penus"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Vignette"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Whirling in Constantinople"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Will You Be the Ape"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--1450-1950 ("Wonder Opened Two Eyes"). (Box 106)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"69". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"A Bit of Biblical Necking". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"A Craven Image". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"A Lot of Bananas, A Bunch of Brains". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"A Poet in Paris". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"A Timid Soul". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Alphabet Soup". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Antiques". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Any Hole". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Aren't Even Allowed to Say Boo". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Atomic Eggs". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Bebop". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Beer". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Birds of Words". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Books, Looks". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Brickette". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Bridal March". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"But I Have No Rhymic Greens". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"But I Know". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Caligulan Calligrams". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Calvary". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Centipede". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Corny!". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Dialects: It's As Simple As This". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Don't Shoot The Author". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Drawing/Dancing". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Einstein". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"First Liberal Lady of the Land". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Gants in the Pants". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"gulf/golf". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"HA! An idea". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Humanity in the Rough". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"I Have Always Meant to Tell Ministers". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"I Will Make Eyes At You". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"If I. Darling". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Intercepted Letters". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"It's a Date!". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Jewels Jesus". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Life in the Wool". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Little Pieces of Paper". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Man, Woman". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Marginalia". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Mercury". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Modern Writing? What'a Ya Mean?". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Moonlight Sonata". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Music Patterns". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"My Atomic Bomb Brain". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"My Spencerian Hand". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"No Bats in my Belfry". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Optical Eye Rhythms". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Optical Music". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Organs/Eyes". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Our Earthly Outlook". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Our Little Egos". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Panama Hat, Panama Canal". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Pastoral". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Peacock Alley". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Piffling Poems". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Piously We Bowl". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Poem to a Poet". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Praying Mantis". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Protoplasm/Ectoplasm". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Punctuation Poems". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Pungent Life". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Quips That Pass in the Night". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Rectangular Red". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Rib Ladder". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Roving Eye Press". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Royal Portrait 18th Century". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Sails". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Salute to All the Bob Browns". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Sanscrit, Hebrew, Ethiopian". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Seed". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Semi-Colon". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Sitting in the Beer Saloon". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Slice My Soul". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Smoke/Drink". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"So, Those Censors". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Steamboat Bill". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Strict, Like a Line". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Sun/Moon". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Supersonic Stratosphere". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Surrealism, Lady Astor". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"That Hole in the Magic Carpet". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"The Alphabet, The Eyelid". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"The Eye Is the Sling". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"the -ments". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"The Pine Has a Cone". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"the well known: colon". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"This is not a Potato". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Thumbnail". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"'til I'm dizzy as an owl". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Time Space Chart". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Tit for Tat". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"To a Portrait Painter". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Verbiage/Garbage". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Vermin in Ermin". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Which Came First: The Egg or the Ego". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Why Should I Read?". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Wish Bone". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Womb, Doom, Tomb". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"WORDSWORDSWORDS". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Writing". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"W-R-I-T-I-N-G". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--"Your Crystalline Self". (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--zz (selected drafts). (Box 107)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Clippings ("Words" by Norman Macleod). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Clippings (article on Apollinaire). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Clippings (color dynamics). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Clippings (On Freezing Speed With a Camera). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Clippings (Portraits by Steinberg). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Clippings (reviews of 1450-1950). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Clippings (visual poems). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--CONTEMPO: A Bob Brown Issue. (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Correspondence. (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Correspondence (James Laughlin, rejection letter re: 1450-1950). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Correspondence (Jonathan Williams, re: publication of 1450-1950). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Correspondence (letter to Menken re: 1450-1950). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Correspondence (Phil Kaplan). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Correspondence (re: Ginsberg, Zukofsky, Levertov). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Correspondence (re: Kenneth Patchen and "picture poems"). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Correspondence (Walter Lowenfels). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Correspondence (William Carlos Williams, re: 1450-1950). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Correspondence and Autobiographical Notes for projected Selected Poems. (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Exhibition Catalog, Ceramics by Picasso. (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Gems (treated notes to Lycidas). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Hilarious Bits of Business (vocabulary). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Notebook. (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Notes ("All Arts Are One"). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Notes ("IDEOLOGY IDEOGRAPH"). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Notes (Alpha Numeric Correspondences). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Notes (list of literary associates to receive free copies of 1450-1950). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Notes (Morgenstern's "Night Song of the Fish"). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Notes (on Neo-Naturism). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Notes (Rhyme Tables). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Notes (Scenarios for "The Moving Finger Writes," proposed TV program). (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Notes/Scrap Paper. (Box 108)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Notes, Drafts, Clippings (on Visual/Verbal analogies). (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Poetics ("A New Hieroglyph"). (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Poetics ("Are Writers Merely Disappointed Painters?"). (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Poetics ("In Defence of Free Verse"). (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Poetics (autobiographical notes on poetry and painting). (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Poetics (comments on 1450-1950). (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Poetics (essay on writing and painting). (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Poetics (lecture notes on proletarian language). (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Poetics (list of historical "writer's books"). (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Poetics (note on Gems published in CONTEMPO). (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Poetics (on "Modern Art"). (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Poetics (on "Primitive Poetry"). (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Poetics (on Free Verse). (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Process Notes. (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Request for Journal Submissions from Modernist Writers. (Box 109)
- Visual/Conceptual Writing--Rough Drafts. (Box 109)
- Photographs--Asia. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Bob and Eleanor Brown in New York. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Bob and Rose Brown "Brazilian American" images. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Bob Brown. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Brazilian riverboat trip. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Brown children [?]. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Carnivale Rio de Janeiro. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Cidade de Petropolis (souvenier booklet). (Box 110)
- Photographs--Eleanor Brown. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Eleanor Brown with friends. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Family and friends [?]. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Family and friends [?]. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Family and friends [?]. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Family images [Cora Brown's?]. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Fishing and water images. (Box 110)
- Photographs--German friends [?]. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Home interior. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Images of various paintings. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Man Ray photo series "Glamor Girls of the Upper Amazon". (Box 110)
- Photographs--Man Ray photos of Bob and Rose Brown for Harper's Bazaar. (Box 110)
- Photographs--Miscellaneous b/w (3.5x2.5). (Box 110)
- Photographs--Miscellaneous b/w (9x7). (Box 110)
- Photographs--Miscellaneous b/w (small prints). (Box 110)
- Photographs--Miscellaneous b/w (various sizes). (Box 110)
- Photographs--Miscellaneous Latin American images. (Box 111)
- Photographs--Miscellaneous Latin American images (various sizes). (Box 111)
- Photographs--Miscellaneous Latin American scenery, sights. (Box 112)
- Photographs--Negatives. (Box 112)
- Photographs--Objects and artifacts. (Box 112)
- Photographs--Portrait of Roy Nash family. (Box 112)
- Photographs--Portraits of family and friends [?] from early 20th century. (Box 112)
- Photographs--Rose Brown. (Box 112)
- Photographs--Russia/USSR. (Box 112)
- Photographs--Snakes. (Box 112)
- Photographs--South American aboriginals. (Box 112)
- Photographs--South American wildlife. (Box 112)
- Photographs--Wild West club. (Box 112)
- Postcards--China/Japan. (Box 112)
- Postcards--Europe. (Box 112)
- Postcards--Miscellaneous. (Box 112)
- Postcards--South American (folder 1 of 2). (Box 112)
- Postcards--South American (folder 2 of 2). (Box 112)
- Brazilian American--documents. (Box 113)
- Brazilian American--Excerpts from various issues. (Box 113)
- Brazilian American--Magazines, clippings, covers. (Box 113)
- Journal excerpt--no Littoral da Goyana Brazileira entre Oyapock e Amazonas. (Box 113)
- Photographs--Miscellaneous Latin American images (oversized). (Box 113)
- Photographs--Various portraits of Bob Brown, Rose Brown, [and Browns' daughter?]. (Box 113)
- Woven artwork. (Box 113)